(Sheldon:)In any event,
(Sheldon:)now that Amy and I have
spent quality time together,
(Sheldon:)I feel much
more confident
(Sheldon:)proceeding to the next
stage of our relationship.
(Penny:)And that is?
(Sheldon:)Using in vitro
fertilization
(Sheldon:)and a surrogate uterus to
gift humanity with our progeny.
(Penny:)You're still
on that?
(Sheldon:)In these uncertain times,
doesn't humanity deserve a gift?
(Penny:)Okay, you know what?
(Penny:)I'm gonna come at this
in a whole new way.
(Penny:)Sheldon, if you try to make
a baby with Amy in a petri dish,
(Penny:)I'm gonna tell
your mother on you.
(Sheldon:)That's no threat.
(Sheldon:)My mother's always
wanted a grandchild.
(Penny:)Really? Your deeply religious
born-again Christian mother
(Penny:)wants a test-tube grandbaby
born out of wedlock?
(Sheldon:)Curses.
(Penny:)If I'd thought of that
in the first place,
(Penny:)I could've saved myself
this whole night.
(Sheldon:)Well, it's not that late.
(Sheldon:)You could still go out
and look for number 32.
(Sheldon:)Good night.
(Leonard(phone rings):)Hey, Howard,
what's up?
(Sheldon:)I've decided
not to procreate.
(Leonard:)Yeah, yeah, great.
(Leonard:)Howard, uh, slow down.
(Leonard:)What do you mean
it happened again?